iaffiliates.com 2016-11-25

# Best Online Casino Affiliate Program | Privacy Policy | iAffiliates |

## Introduction

"We", "our", "us" means Mansion (Gibraltar) Ltd which provides marketing services to a number of brands operated by its Group, or the relevant company in the Group as the case may be. "You", "your", and/or "affiliate" mean the individual or entity that has agreed to promote us in return for bounties and/or commissions on the players that are referred to us in accordance with these terms.

We have provided this privacy policy to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard your information and those of the players referred by you to us for the purpose of operating our online casino and poker services. You should read this notice in conjunction with our terms and conditions for use of this site or any other sites operated by us.

## Personal information

We collect personal information when you and /or your referred players as appropriate use our online gambling services, join our affiliate program, make customer enquiries, register for information or other services, or when you respond to us. Selected third parties, to whom you and /or your referred players as appropriate have chosen to disclose personal information, may also provide us with personal information. The types of personal information we may collect could include, for example, your name and e-mail address, home address, telephone number, debit/credit card data and lifestyle and other information collected on registration or through online surveys or questionnaires.

We may publicize any major winnings earned by your players by simply giving their username, country of origin, amount of winning and associated game - whereby you agree to this limited use of their details for this sole purpose, unless you otherwise contact us to demonstrate that your players wish to revoke such implied consent, where we will then follow up with them.

## How your and/or your referred players' information is processed

Your and/or your referred players information may be disclosed for processing to any other companies within the Group and their employees; any third party service providers who use your and/or your referred players personal information to provide services to us - such as: payment settlement service providers, marketing service providers, data verifiers and financial institutions, to the extent necessary for the completion of payments, joint marketing campaigns, facilitate the opening of new accounts, and fraud prevention for services provided through our website; or any auditors or contractors or other advisers auditing any of the Group's business processes, potential purchasers or investors in any company within the Group. Any processing performed by any recipients will be governed by the necessary data processing agreement in the form and substance required by applicable law, thereby preserving your and/or your referred players rights under applicable data protection laws.

## Your responsibility towards your referred players

If you yourself receive and process personal information from players that you subsequently refer to us then you shall ensure that they have given their express consent to such transfer to us and this personal information is processed and transferred by you to us in accordance with relevant laws but in any event under terms no less stringent that those set out herein. You agree to indemnify us against all claims and associated costs brought against and suffered by us due to your breach of this clause.

## To whom your and/or your referred players information is disclosed ("recipients")

We ensure that your and/or you referred players information will not be disclosed to government institutions or authorities unless:

  * we have your and/or your referred players written consent to share such personally identifiable information with third parties;
  * we require your and/or your referred players personally identifiable information to provide the services that you have requested (if any)
  * we respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process;
  * we find that your and/or your referred players actions on our web sites violate our terms of service, or any of our and/or you referred players usage guidelines for specific services.

In addition, we reserve the right to disclose and transfer your and/or your referred players personal data to our respective payment settlement service providers and financial institutions to the extent necessary for the completion of payments for services provided through our website.

## Security

Keeping your and/or your referred players' data safe is our paramount concern.

Internal access to all data is limited and strictly monitored. We have implemented suitable security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard the personal data under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss.

All our employees and data processors or handlers who have access to, and are associated with the processing of your and/or your referred players personal information, are obliged to respect the confidential nature of your and/or you referred players information pursuant to applicable data protection and privacy laws.

## Cookies

We may send you and/or your referred players a permanent cookie when you or they register with us. A cookie is a small file that can be placed on your and/or your referred players’ computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can help us to recognise you and/or your referred players when you or they next visit our website, note the advertisements you or they click on and the other sites you or they enter via a link from our website. This allows us to tailor the service we provide to your or their preferences. We may also use the data generated from cookies to compile statistical data on your and/or your referred players use of our website. You and/or your referred players are not obliged to accept a cookie from us or from any other website. You and/or your referred players can modify your browsers so that it will not accept cookies. Please consult the "Help" section of your and/or you referred players browser for instructions on how to do so correctly. However, for legitimate security reasons, we may refuse access to specific website content unless you and/or you referred players accept the use of a cookie or similar device.

## Protection of Minors

The services provided on this website are not intended for or directed to minors or persons under the age of legal consent. Any person who provides their information to us represents to us that they are 18 years of age or over the age of legal consent in their jurisdiction. We reserve the right to access and verify any personal information submitted by or collected from your referred players. If we become aware that a minor has attempted to or has submitted personal information via this website, we may not accept this information and may take steps to remove such information from our records.

## Transfer outside the European Union

It may be necessary to transfer your and/or your referred players personal information to other companies within the Group located in countries outside the European Union. This may happen if any of our servers or members of the Group are located or based outside the European Union, if you and/or your referred players use our services and products while visiting countries outside the European Union or if we transfer your or their personal information to such companies for purposes regarding which you or they will receive advance notice. The data protection, privacy and other laws of these non-European Union countries may not be as comprehensive and in these instances we will take steps to ensure that a similar level of protection is given to your and/or your referred players information. We reserve the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation applicable to the Group. By submitting your and/or your referred players personally identifiable information to us you and they consent to the use of that information as set out in this Privacy Policy. If we change our Privacy Policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you and/or your referred players may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes made so please check this page regularly.

## Contact us

You may request details of your and/or your referred players personal information kept by us by following the contact information set out below. Once we receive such a request we will ask you and/or your referred players to verify you or their identity by providing relevant information or documentation. We will then request pre-payment of an administration fee of US$15 per request and upon receipt of this we will process your and/or your referred players' request within 40 days.

If you have any enquiry about our data protection and privacy policy or practices, or wish to decline receiving e-mail offers from us or from any other companies within the Group please contact affiliates support by email to [support@iaffiliates.com](mailto:support@iaffiliates.com) or write to iaffiliates.com at Suite 901, Europort, Gibraltar.

This privacy policy was last revised on the 2nd November 2011
